

Covington, WA 98042 akshayduggal531@gmail.com 2063795835

Reliable, Professional, eager go getter and Tech savvy. Desktop technical support background 2+ years. PC Deployment and Troubleshooting Experience 2+ years.

Fluent Communication in three languages English, Hindi and Punabi, 6+ year customer service Experience.

Completed Associates degree in Networking And Cyber security.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Help Desk

MultiCare Health System - Tukwila, WA

September 2020 to Present

Provide Tier 2 support for all desktop, laptop, phone and other computing equipment. Participate in the diagnosis and resolution of problems in response to customer reported incident. Participate in the planning and delivery of technical support services, including troubleshooting, installation, removals, moves, customer assistance, and/or training, in response to customer requirements. Manage service requests via ticket tracking system. Create documentation for desktop setup, maintenance, repair and asset tracking. Set up equipment for employee use, ensuring proper functionality. Prepare evaluations of software or hardware, and recommend improvements or upgrades.

IT Help Desk

Moblie work integrations - Tukwila, WA January 2020 to June 2020

Serving as the first point of contact for customers seeking technical assistance over the phone or email or in person. Performing remote troubleshooting through diagnostic techniques, provide accurate information on IT products and services. Imaging and installing Kaiser Permanente workstations, Kiosk and shared Computers using Infoblox and App OS. Monitor incoming customer technical service requests via email, phone, and ticketing system software. Troubleshooting Office 365, 2016, and 2010 deployment and troubleshooting. Log and track all technical support interactions into the ticketing. Providing both Tier I /II support face-to-face and on call for customers.

EDUCATION

license in FA/CPR/AED and BLS

American Heart Association - Tacoma, WA September 2020 to October 2020

Associate in Networking And Cyber security

Green River Community College - Auburn, WA February 2018 to July 2020

some school in Nursing

nursing assistant school - Tukwila, WA June 2019 to June 2019

SKILLS

- · Active Directory
- Desktop Support
- · Help Desk
- · Microsoft Windows
- Network Support
- Operating Systems
- Software Troubleshooting
- Technical Support
- · Microsoft Office
- Team Management
- Punctual
- Hardworking
- Microsoft Outlook